Guide to the World Trade Organization 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference Protest Collection
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- World Trade Organization, 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference Protest Collection, 1993-2000; 5177-003; 31.17 cubic feet 15 boxes, 3 tubes, 5 oversized objects
  - PEOPLE FOR FAIR TRADE/NO TO WTO, RECORDS SUBGROUP VI
    - Part 2: During WTO
      - Subject Series
        - Food and Agriculture Day, 1999 (Box-folder 3/40)
        - Infernal Noise Brigade (Box-folder 10/2)
        - Medics—Re Basic Medic Kit, 11/22/99 (Box-folder 3/41)
        - Oleoresin Capsicum (Pepper Spray), 11/30/99 (Box-folder 3/42)
        - Protest Targets, 1999 (Box-folder 3/43)
        - Seattle International Peoples’ Assembly, 1999 (Box-folder 3/44)
        - Volunteers, 11/28-12/3/99 (Box-folder 3/45)
        - Women, Development, Democracy Day at WTO, 1999 (Box-folder 3/46)
        - WTO Ministerial, 1999 (Box-folder 3/47)
      - Publications
        - Belltown’s Regrade Dispatch, 12/12/99 (Box-folder 3/48)
        - The Spectator (Seattle University), 12/2/99 (Box-folder 3/49)
      - Newsletters (Box-folder 3/50)
      - News Releases (Box-folder 3/51)
      - Maps (Box-folder 3/52)
      - Map OVERSIZED, Large map of downtown Seattle used by the Direct Action Network in planning the shut-down of downtown Seattle Nov. 30, with the Convention Center at the epicenter and "pie slices" radiating outward; each of these slices was adopted by an "affinity group" or "cluster" of affinity groups and it was their responsibility to blockade their particular slice. (Tube:oversize 18)
      - Photographs (Box-folder 3/53)
      - Financial Records (Box-folder 3/54)
      - Ephemera (Box-folder 3/55-57)
      - Artifacts
        - Armband, black, reads: “City-Wide Walkout” (Box-folder 11/2)
        - Bumper Stickers (Box-folder 11/3)
        - Buttons (Box-folder 11/4)
        - Cigarettes (presented to people released from jail) (Box-folder 11/5)
        - Hat, Parade Marshall’s (Box-folder 11/6)
        - Particulate Mask
        - Photograph of Dee Dee Rainbow, autographed (Box-folder 11/8)
        - Police Tape (false) reads: “Unseen Crimes” (Box-folder 11/9)
        - Swim Goggles (Box-folder 11/10)
        - T-Shirt, black, torn piece (Box-folder 11/11)
        - Item list, with notes, by Jeremy Simer (Box-folder 11/12)
      - Posters OVERSIZED
        - Calendars (Box-folder 13/1)
        - “Fremont/Ballard Neighborhood” (Box-folder 13/2)
        - Handmade sign announcing opening of Network Opposed To World Trade Organization offices
        - Agenda (Handmade sign)
        - “Showdown In Seattle”
        - “Congratulations, Seattle”
        - “The Golf War”
        - Miscellaneous Posters distributed by Dana Schuerholz (Box-folder 13/3)
        - Sierra Club (Box-folder 13/4)
          - “The Grinch Who Stole Christmas”
          - “Make Trade Clean, Green, and Fair”
          - “No Globalization”
        - “Tell Schell” (Box-folder 13/5)
        - “Stop the Corporate World Takeover”
        - “Benefit!”
        - “Beyond the WTO Ministerial”
        - “Do You Know?”
        - “That’s Right, Tiffany” (Box-folder 13/6)
        - “Nine Things to Do”
        - “Shhhhhh”
        - World Trade Organization (Turtle)
        - “Defend Free Speech” (Handmade Poster) (Box-folder 13/7)
        - “Fair Trade”
        - “Food and Agriculture Day”
        - “Stop the WTO!”
        - “We Believe in Fair Trade, How About You, Al Gore?”
      - Banner OVERSIZED (Box-folder Tube 16)
        - “WTO Hurts Working Families--Seattle Center Rally and Meeting Nov. 30/1999 8 am” (street banner—white with red Letters—airflow cuts)
    - Part 3: Post-WTO
      - Minutes, 12/13/99 (Box-folder 3/58)
      - Incoming Letters, 12/7/99-7/28/00 (Box-folder 3/59)
      - Outgoing Letter (Box-folder 3/60)
      - Speeches and Writings - Atkin, Jerry, Jobs With Justice, undated (Box-folder 3/61)
      - Subject Series
        - N30 Mural Project (Box-folder 3/62)
        - Views on Food and Agriculture Day (Box-folder 3/63)
      - Newsletter - World Affairs, 12/99 (Box-folder 3/64)
      - Publications
        - Bringing Democracy Home, 4/2000 (Box-folder 3/65)
        - Rebuild the Balkans, 7/1999 (Box-folder 3/66)
        - Standing, 3/2000 (Box-folder 3/67)
      - Report - Seattle International Peoples’ Assembly—Report from the Secretariat, 1/00-2/00 (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Web Page Printouts
        - Eat the State (Box-folder 4/2)
        - Pure Food (Box-folder 4/3)
        - World Socialist (Box-folder 4/4)
        - World Trade Organization (Box-folder 4/5)
      - Ephemera – re: Celebration of Victory (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Ephemera (Box-folder 4/7-8)
  - PUBLIC CITIZEN'S GLOBAL TRADE WATCH, RECORDS SUBGROUP VII
    - Part 1: Pre-WTO
      - Organization (Box-folder 4/9)
      - Outgoing Letter, 8/31/99 (Box-folder 4/10)
      - Contact Lists – Environmental and Health Day (Box-folder 4/11)
      - Packet – “WTO: What Are We Trading Away?”, undated (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Subject Series - Michael Moore, Director of WTO, 10/1/1999 (Box-folder 4/13)
      - Newsletters
        - Eco WTO Watch, 4/99 (Box-folder 4/14)
        - Harmonization Alert, 11/98, 6/99-7/99 (Box-folder 4/15)
      - News Releases (Box-folder 4/16)
      - Speeches and Writings
        - Nader, Ralph & Lori Wallach, “GATT, NAFTA, and the Subversion of the Democratic Process”, undated (Box-folder 4/17)
        - Parrish, Geov, “Shutting Down Seattle”, 8/19/99 (Box-folder 4/18)
        - Wallach, Lori M., International ‘Harmonization’ of Social, Economic, and Environmental Standards, 7/98 (Box-folder 4/19)
        - Wallach, Lori M., Testimony of Lori Wallach, Global Trade Watch, Re: U.S. Preparations for the WTO’s 1999 Ministerial Meeting, 8/5/99 (Box-folder 4/20)
        - “Comments of Public Citizen…”, 10/22/98 (Box-folder 4/21)
        - “Five-Year Record of WTO Reveals Disturbing Trends: Food Safety, Environment Undermined, Accountable Governance Eroded”, 10/13/99 (Box-folder 4/22)
        - Statement of Joan Claybrook on WTO, 10-13-99
        - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 4/23)
      - Publications
        - Anderson, Alfred F., Challenging Newt Gingrich, 1996 (Box-folder 4/24)
        - A Citizen’s Guide To The World Trade Organization, 7/99 (Box-folder 4/25)
      - Ephemera (Box-folder 4/26)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 4/27)
    - Part 2: During WTO
      - Schedule (Box-folder 4/28)
      - Newsletter - Mobilization Against Corporate Globalization, 11/29-12/3/00 (Box-folder 4/29)
      - News Releases (Box-folder 4/30)
  - ALAN RABINOWITZ, RECORDS SUBGROUP VIII
    - E-mail On Floppy Disk With Printouts—“65 Files Plus Early Newspaper Clippings.” Includes Copy Of The Fake Seattle Post-intelligence Of 11/30/99, 7 – 12/99 (Box-folder 9/1-8)
    - Part 1: Pre-WTO
      - Incoming Letters
        - International Forum on Globalization, 10/22/98-11/17/99 (Box-folder 4/31)
        - Miscellaneous, 2/20-11/21/99 (Box-folder 4/32)
      - Outgoing Letter, 4/12/99 (Box-folder 4/33)
      - Audiocassettes: (Box-folder 4/34)
        - Making Contact, Democracy for Sale, 7/7/99
        - World Trade Watch Demo Tape, undated
      - Subject Series – Institute For Agriculture and Trade Policy
        - Incoming Letters, 1/27/99-8/10/99 (Box-folder 4/35)
        - Annual Reports, 1996-97, 98-99 (Box-folder 4/36)
        - Newsletters
          - Agriculture Biodiversity News, 11/98-3/99 (Box-folder 4/37)
          - The Road to Seattle Issue VII, 9/10/99 (Box-folder 4/38)
          - IPR---info: Information About Intellectual Property Rights, 5/95-7/98 (Box-folder 4/39)
        - Proceedings - Meeting on the WTO Agreement on Agriculture, 9/30-10/4/98 (Box-folder 4/40)
        - Speeches and Writings
          - Dawkins, Kristen, “Defending Biological Diversity and Food Security in the Face of Globalization”, 11/97 (Box-folder 4/41)
          - Dawkins, Kristen, “Trade Strategy of U.S.: Analysis of Current Agricultural Policy”, 1/8/99 (Box-folder 4/42)
          - Dawkins, Kristen & Steve Suppan, Sterile Fields: The Impacts of Intellectual Property Rights and Trade on Biodiversity & Food Security, 11/96 (Box-folder 4/43)
          - Hausknost, Daniel, “In Europe, Consumers Think Twice: A look at the Uproar Over Genetically Engineered Food”, 7/10/98 (Box-folder 4/44)
          - Kraker, Daniel & Kristen Dawkins, “The Continuing Threat From Trade Negotiations”, 3/99 (Box-folder 4/45)
          - Lehman, Karen, “Alternatives To The Global Trading System For Agriculture”, 5/16/96 (Box-folder 4/46)
          - Murphy, Sophia, “Trade and Food Security—An Assessment Of the Uruguay Round Agreement on Agriculture”, 1999 (Box-folder 4/47)
          - Murphy, Sophia, Trade-Related Agenda, Development and Equity (Trade) Working Papers, 11/99 (Box-folder 4/48)
          - Teitel, M., Fund, C.S., and H. Shand, The Ownership of Life, When Patents and Values Clash, 6/97 (Box-folder 4/49)
          - “Building the ‘capacity to trade’ through trade related policy reform: Towards revising the Agreement on Agriculture and the Agreement on Trade-Related Aspects of Intellectual Property Rights”, 9/8/97 (Box-folder 4/50)
          - “Strengthening Complementarities Between Trade, Environment and Sustainable Development”, 3/17-18/98 (Box-folder 4/51)
        - Ephemera (Box-folder 4/52)
        - Subject Series - International Forum on Globalization
        - Audiotapes - Teach-In, 11/26/99 (Box-folder 4/53)
        - Report - Beyond the WTO, Alternatives to Economic Globalization, 11/26/99 (Box-folder 4/54)
        - Partial Summary of Media Coverage—IFG WTO Campaign, undated (Box-folder 4/55)
        - Speeches and Writings (Publications)
          - Barker, D. & J. Mander, Invisible Government, 10/99 (Box-folder 4/56)
          - Barlow, Maude, Blue Gold, 6/99 (Box-folder 4/57)
          - Newsletters, 10-11/99 (Box-folder 4/58)
          - Publications (Box-folder 4/59)
        - Speeches and Writings by Others
          - Ad Hoc Working Group on the MAI, “ MAI—Democracy For Sale?”, undated (Box-folder 4/60)
          - Shrybman, Steven, “The World Trade Organization: The New World Constitution Laid Bare”, undated (Box-folder 4/61)
          - Cuernavaca Consensus—Draft, undated (Box-folder 4/62)
          - “Solidar Briefing”, 11/99 (Box-folder 4/63)
      - Ephemera (Box-folder 4/64)
      - Clippings (Box-folder 4/65)
    - Part 2: During WTO
      - Audiocassettes - World Trade Watch, Five Days of the WTO (10 tapes total, 2 sets), 11/29-12/3/99 (Box-folder 4/66-67)
      - Workshop - Institute for Agriculture & Trade Policy on Trade-Related Aspects of Intellectual Property Rights (TRIPS), 11/30/98 (Box-folder 4/68)
      - Publications (Box-folder 4/69)
      - Ephemera (Box-folder 4/70)
      - Clippings (Box-folder 4/71)
    - Part 3: Post-WTO
      - Incoming Letters (Box-folder 5/1)
        - World Trade Watch, 12/11/99
        - International Forum On Globalization, 12/20/99
      - Outgoing Letter, 2/1/2000 (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Newsletters, Feb-Apr/2000 (Box-folder 5/3)
      - Publications (Box-folder 5/4-5)
      - Clippings (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Ephemera (Box-folder 5/7)
        - “The Whole World Is Watching, Art, Images & Literature From The WTO Protests” Center On Contemporary Art Exhibit Brochure
        - Misc.
  - SEATTLE HOST ORGANIZATION: NGO COMMITTEE, RECORDS SUBGROUP IX:
    - Organization (Box-folder 5/8)
    - Incoming Letters
      - Wiehoff, Dale e-mail, 2/17/99 (Box-folder 5/9)
      - To Goldman, Patti, 8/6/-11/24/99 (Box-folder 5/10)
    - Outgoing Letter (Box-folder 5/11)
    - Calendars (Box-folder 5/12)
    - Packets
      - Corporate Hospitality (Box-folder 5/13)
      - Delegates’ (Box-folder 5/14)
    - Agenda - Trade And Environment Session, 12/2/1999 (Box-folder 5/15)
    - Ephemera (Box-folder 5/16)
  - Part 1: Pre-WTO
    - Historical Features – World Trade Organization (Box-folder 5/17)
    - Incoming Letter – Fidel Castro To Jim Mcdermott, 11/29/99 (Box-folder 5/18)
    - Outgoing Letter – Church Council Of Greater Seattle To Castro, 10/1/99 (Box-folder 5/19)
    - Calendar (Box-folder 5/20)
    - Packets/handbooks
      - Alliance For Better Foods (Box-folder 5/21)
      - Body Shop – “Wasting Trade Opportunities” (Box-folder 5/22)
      - Global Environmental Protection (Box-folder 5/23)
      - Greenpeace International (Box-folder 5/24)
      - “A Handbook of World Trade” MinComEx Columbia (Box-folder 5/25)
      - Preamble Center (Box-folder 5/26)
      - National Wildlife Federation (Box-folder 5/27)
      - World Bank Bonds Boycott Campaign (Box-folder 5/28)
    - Subject Series
      - Alliance For Democracy (Box-folder 5/29)
      - American Lands Alliance, 8/6/99 (Box-folder 5/30)
      - Asia Pacific Center for Justice and Peace, 1998-99 (Box-folder 5/31)
      - Coffee (Box-folder 5/32)
      - Falun Gong, 11/99 (Box-folder 5/33)
      - Friends Of The Earth, 1999 (Box-folder 5/34-35)
      - Grassroots International (Box-folder 5/36)
      - Green Party, 1999 (Box-folder 5/37)
      - International Federation for Alternative Trade (Box-folder 5/38)
      - Manana Coalition, 10/5/99 (Box-folder 5/39)
      - No On I-695 Campaign (Box-folder 5/40)
      - Pacific Northwest Junior State (Box-folder 5/41)
      - Ruckus Society (Box-folder 5/42)
      - Seattle Anarchist Response (Box-folder 5/43)
      - Seeds Of Liberation (Box-folder 5/44)
      - Sierra Club (Box-folder 5/45)
      - United For a Fair Economy (Box-folder 5/46)
      - U.S. Chamber of Commerce (Box-folder 5/47-49)
      - U.S. Congress (Box-folder 5/50)
      - Women and Trade (Box-folder 5/51)
      - Women’s International League for Peace and Freedom (Box-folder 5/52)
      - WTO Student Ambassador Program (Box-folder 5/53)
    - News Releases (Box-folder 5/54)
    - Publications
      - The Big Picture, Visualizing The Global Economy (Box-folder 5/55)
      - Compost The Corporations
      - The Dispatcher
      - Dossier—Medicines
      - Eat The State, 3-11/1999 (Box-folder 5/56)
      - Eugene Weekly (Box-folder 5/57)
      - European Public Health Update
      - Handbook For Nonviolent Action
      - Infusion
      - Instant Planet
      - Real Change, 8-11/1999 (Box-folder 5/58)
      - Seattle Weekly (Box-folder 5/59)
      - Storm Warning! (Box-folder 5/60)
      - Street Roots
      - Teamsters On The Front Line—Local 174
      - Trade Union World
      - The World Bank
      - Z Magazine
    - Speeches And Writings
      - Canwright, Lois, “Action Advice & Globalization and the WTO”, undated (Box-folder 5/61)
      - Godfried, Mike, “WTO Talking Points”, undated (Box-folder 5/62)
      - History Committee of the General Strike Committee, The Seattle General Strike of 1919, 1999 (Box-folder 5/63)
      - Stanton, Arnold, “Ode: To All Oligarchs And Their Minions”, 1998 (Box-folder 5/64)
      - Japan Proposal, “Toward the Establishment of Trade Rules For the 21st Century that Contribute to the Era of Diversity And Coexistence”, undated (Box-folder 5/65)
      - Japan Proposal, “Proposal of Japan on the WTO Negotiations” (Box-folder 5/66)
      - Legal Opinion re Child Labor Laws & Gatt, 7/15/93 (Box-folder 5/67)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 5/68)
    - Brochures
      - Consumers International, “Consumer Rights and the Multilateral Trading System”, 8/99 (Box-folder 5/69)
      - Environmental Media Services, “Understanding International Trade and the Environment”, undated (Box-folder 5/70)
      - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, “Building Workers’ Human Rights Into the Global Trading System”, 1999 (Box-folder 5/71)
      - Royal Society For The Prevention Of Cruelty To Animals (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Trans Atlantic Consumer Dialogue (TACD), 10/99 (Box-folder 6/2)
      - United States Trade Representative (Box-folder 6/3)
      - World Vision (Box-folder 6/4)
    - Newsletters
      - Socialist (Box-folder 6/5)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 6/6-7)
    - Report – U.s. Trade Representative – “accelerated Tariff Liberalization…”, 11/99 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Lists
      - Labor & NGO Allies, undated (Box-folder 6/9)
      - Seattle Public Library reading list (Box-folder 6/10)
    - Ephemera
      - Revolutionary Communist Party U.S.A. Seattle Branch (Box-folder 6/11)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 6/12-17)
    - Clippings (Box-folder 6/18-20)
  - Part 2:During WTO
    - Packets
      - Delegate Packet (Box-folder 6/21)
      - Press Pack (Box-folder 6/22)
      - European Union Millennium Round Packet (Box-folder 6/23)
      - Seattle Round Agricultural Committee Media Packet (Box-folder 6/24)
    - Personal Accounts (Box-folder 6/25-40)
    - Subject Series
      - Citizens For Free Trade, undated (Box-folder 6/41)
      - Civil Disobedience (Box-folder 6/42)
      - Independent Media Center (incl. Newsletter – Blind Spot, A Daily Bulletin Of Underreported Anti-WTO Activism, Issues 1-5) (Box-folder 6/43)
      - Ephemera
      - Industrial Workers Of The World, 11/99-1/00 (Box-folder 6/44)
      - Seattle, City of (Box-folder 6/45)
      - Seattle Police Department, 11/30/99,n.d. (Box-folder 6/46)
      - United Steelworkers of America (Box-folder 6/47)
      - Vietnam Veterans Against the War Anti-Imperialist (Box-folder 6/48)
      - Washington Toxics Coalition, 11/28/99, n.d. (Box-folder 6/49)
    - Court Paper, 12/2/99 (Box-folder 6/50)
    - Cartoons (Box-folder 6/51)
    - Comics Oversized (Box-folder 12/1)
    - Publications
      - Seattle Post Intelligence (Parody), 11/30/99 (Box-folder 6/52)
      - Washington Free Press, 11-12/99 (Box-folder 6/53)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 6/54)
    - Publications (WTO Week Accounts)
      - Labor Press (Box-folder 6/55)
      - Socialist Press (Box-folder 6/56)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 6/57-7/1)
    - Newsletters
      - Bridges, Daily Update On The Third Ministerial Conference, 12/3/99 (Box-folder 7/2)
      - The Current, 7/99-8/99 (Box-folder 7/3)
      - Environment & Climate News, 2/2000 (Box-folder 7/4)
      - GovLink WTO Traffic Alerts, 12/1-8/99 (Box-folder 7/5)
      - Puget Sound Council Of Senior Citizens, 10/99-1/00 (Box-folder 7/6)
      - WTO Watch, 12/99 (Box-folder 7/7)
    - Speeches And Writings
      - Clinton, Wm. J., Remarks by the President at the Signing of ILO Convention 182, 12/2/99 (Box-folder 7/8)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 7/9)
    - News Release - Caribbean Community (Box-folder 7/10)
    - Programs (Box-folder 7/11)
      - “GMOs and the World Trade Organization: Food For Thought”, 12/1/99
      - “Seattle Symposium On International Trade Issues In The First Decades Of The Next Century”, 12/1/99
    - Photographs (Box-folder 7/12-13)
    - Conferences And Conventions
      - ICFTU Conference on Globalisation and Workers’ Rights: Core Labour Standards in the Global Economy, 11/28-29/99 (Box-folder 7/14)
      - LELO—Workers’ Voices Coalition, 12/4/99 (Box-folder 7/15)
    - Ephemera
      - Events (Box-folder 7/16)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 7/17)
    - Clippings (Box-folder 7/18-20)
    - Artifacts Oversized
      - Plastic WTO Rain Ponchos (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Black & Yellow “Insurrection” Banner (Box-folder 12/3)
      - Turtle Costumes (Box-folder 23)
    - Picket Signs Oversized
      - Darth Vader, on a stick (Box-folder 19)
      - “Reclaim The Streets”, on a stick (Box-folder 20)
      - Tear Gas Canister, on a stick (Box-folder 21)
      - Tree, on a stick (Box-folder 22)
    - Posters Oversized
      - WTO Octopus (Box-folder 15/4)
      - “First Amendment” (Box-folder 12/4)
      - “Expose & Oppose the WTO”
      - “Nov. 30 No To WTO! People’s Assembly March & Rally”
      - “WTO Basta!”
      - “Junk WTO”
      - “Congratulations Everyone” with Post-Intelligencer Front Page, 12/4/99 (Box-folder 14/2)
      - No To WTO
      - “Stop the Global Gamblers,” Foamboard (Box-folder 14/3)
      - Union-Related Posters
        - “Labor Says WTO Ends Democracy”
        - Firefighters Logo, Foamboard
        - Teamsters Local 174—“No To WTO”
      - Sweatshops (GAP) (Box-folder 14/4)
      - Make Trade Green, Clean, and Fair (3)
      - Trade/Debt “Boomerangs”
      - Economic Institutionalized Racism
      - Seattle Police Department Training
      - Stop the WTO (Box-folder 14/5)
      - Art and Revolution Convergence
      - Horsey 1999 Post-Intelligencer Cartoon (enlarged photocopy) (Box-folder 14/6)
      - Poetry Event
      - Poem by Eric Larson
      - Training Posters
  - Part 3: Post-WTO
    - Subject Series
      - China Admission To WTO, 12/99 (Box-folder 8/1)
      - Seattle. City Council Hearings, 12/99 – 1/00 (Box-folder 8/2)
    - Speeches And Writings (Box-folder 8/3)
      - “Funder’s Network On Trade Globalization, Background Information”, 3/00
    - Publicatons
      - Eat The State, 12/99-2/00 (Box-folder 8/4)
      - Fifth Estate, Spring 2000
      - Leschi News, 12/99, 1/00 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - People’s Weekly World, 12/99 – 1/00 (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Washington Free Press, Jan-Feb. 2000 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Z Magazine, 1/00 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Spanish Language (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 8/10)
    - Ephemera (Box-folder 8/11-14)
    - Clippings (Box-folder 8/15-16)
    - Posters Oversized
      - Jubilee 2000 (Box-folder 12/5)
      - N30 “We will not be silenced”
      - N30 Whose Day? Our Day!
      - Anarchist Teach-In Handmade Posters (2), 3/2000 (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Oversized Material (as Described Above) (Box-folder 12-23)
- World Trade Organization, 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference Protest Collection, 5177-004; 2.33 cubic feet 2 boxes; includes 5 videotapes
  Posters, videotapes, ephemera, and published material. Videotapes include the four-part video "Labor Beat: WTO Seattle."
  Open to all users.
  Donated 2/22/2001.
- World Trade Organization, 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference Protest Collection, 1998-2000 December; 1999 August-2000 December; 5177-005; .42 cubic feet 1 box
  Ephemera, publications, clippings, relating to the April 16, 2000 protest against the IMF at World Bank meeting in Washington D.C.,and the WTO demonstrations in Seattle; minutes of one post-WTO mtg, People for Fair Trade, transcript of radio program of a teach-in, 11/99, "The Day the WTO Stood Still," and a report by the ACLU of Washington on official responses to the Seattle protests.
  Donated 3/26/2001.
- World Trade Organization, 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference Protest Collection, 1999 October-2000 December; 1999 November-December; 5177-006; 1.42 cubic feet 4 boxes; Includes 14 videocassettes (VHS) and 1 compact disc sound recording
  Ephemera, videotaped speeches, independently produced videotapes of programs prior to and programs following the 1999 meetings in Seattle, compact disc recording of protest songs, T-shirt, publications, press releases.
  Donated 7/5/2001.
- World Trade Organization, 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference Protest Collection, 1999-1999; 5177-007; .42 cubic feet 1 box
  Ephemera, publications, clippings, email, newsletters, news releases, documenting various opposition groups' preparations for the WTO round in Seattle, WTO week protests and events, and the aftermath.
  Donated 8/16/2001.
- World Trade Organization, 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference Protest Collection, 2000; 5177-008; .42 cubic feet 1 box
  Oral history transcripts of the WTO History Project.
  Donated 9/25/2001.
- WTO Seattle collection, 1999; 5177-009; 0.42 cubic feet 1 box